{
    "id": "2e314b32bda24e8dad285ece583137ea",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I always feel ............................... in the afternoon.",
            "description": "Feel is a copular verb. We use adjectives to modify copular verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "sleepy",
                "sleepily",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I .............................. her till twelve, and then went home.",
            "description": "Before an object, we use wait for.",
            "answers": [
                "expected",
                "waited",
                "waited for"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ................................ her to turn up soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expecting",
                "waiting",
                "hoping"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They talk such ...............................!",
            "description": "Nonsense is uncountable. It cannot be used with a.",
            "answers": [
                "nonsense",
                "a nonsense",
                "nonsenses"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Every one of the guests .............................. dancing.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after every one.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I go there every ...............................",
            "description": "Every should be followed by a singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "day",
                "days",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I see her every few ..................................",
            "description": "Every is used with plural nouns in expressions that refer to intervals.",
            "answers": [
                "day",
                "days"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoy ............................... in the rain.",
            "description": "Enjoy is followed by an ing form. ",
            "answers": [
                "walking",
                "to walk",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It was Sam ............................... bought the tickets.",
            "description": "That cannot be used to refer to people in non-identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks ........................... older than she used to.",
            "description": "Very cannot be used with comparatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ................................ meet in the cafeteria in the evenings.",
            "description": "Either would or used to can be used to talk about past habits. ",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Let's meet ............................... next week.",
            "description": "Sometime refers to an indefinite time in future. ",
            "answers": [
                "sometime",
                "some time",
                "sometimes"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}